<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Announcement Social Post</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>forcebrain__IME_Letterhead</letterhead>
    <name>Order Fulfillment Product Delivered - Social Post_Announcement_TEAM</name>
    <style>formalLetter</style>
    <subject>Your Five Star Professional announcement post has been published!</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello {!NullValue(Order_Fulfillment__c.Display_Contact_First_Name__c&quot;)}:

A new social post has been published for you! Please check out your new post online and share it directly to your network to optimize the views and interactions.

Your post can be viewed here: {!Order_Fulfillment__c.Product_Delivered_Link__c}

Additionally, we encourage you to share the following announcement email with your clients and network. Just copy/paste the content below into an email or other digital announcement platform to share.

If you have any questions, please don&apos;t hesitate to reach out to your Client Success Representative, {!Order_Fulfillment__c.Fulfillment_Owner_Fullname__c}, at {!Order_Fulfillment__c.Fulfillment_Owner_Phone__c} or by email at {!Order_Fulfillment__c.Fulfillment_Owner_Email__c}.

Thank you,
Five Star Professional Client Success Team
Five Star Professional is pleased to announce that {!Order_Fulfillment__c.Display_Team_Name__c} are {!Order_Fulfillment__c.Market_Award_Year__c} {!Order_Fulfillment__c.Associated_With__c}s! {!Fulfillment__c.Display_Team_Name__c} are among an elite group of professionals honored with the Five Star award in the {!Order_Fulfillment__c.Market_Region__c} area.

The {!NullValue(Order_Fulfillment__c.Associated_With__c&quot;)} award recognizes professionals who excel in client satisfaction. All award winners are chosen after undergoing rigorous research, including client nominations and evaluations, regulatory requirements, and a review by an industry Blue Ribbon Panel. After satisfying all of our research requirements, {!Order_Fulfillment__c.Display_Team_Name__c} have been named as {!NullValue(Order_Fulfillment__c.Associated_With__c&quot;)}s!

Please join me in congratulating {!Order_Fulfillment__c.Display_Team_Name__c} on this incredible accomplishment. You can see a congratulations post here!
Jonathan Wesser
Five Star Professional
VP, Research</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
